<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Retirement Practice</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Retirement Practice</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 13:21:23 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lessons Learned from a Two Tour Bicycle Tourer</title><link>/posts/my-second-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 13:21:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/my-second-post/</guid><description>
It’s four am. I’m in the middle of Switzerland cowboy camping directly off a bicycle path in a small forested area. I’m laying on top of a tent, which we decided to use as a tarp as we were too tired and lazy to set it up, cursing the existence of god damn mosquitos, who buzzed around sounding like mini jet engines taking off. I’m wearing long johns under my pants, wool socks, shoes, a long sleeve, a puffer jacket, a beanie, a gator covering my face, three tshirts on top of my legs forming a shit makeshift blanket, a tshirt wrapped around my feet because those needle nose pricks are biting me through my wool socks.</description></item><item><title>Quick Travel Summary</title><link>/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 13:21:23 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="/images/nathanheader2.jpg"/>
Hello hello party people!! I have a whole lot to catch everyone up on. The last thing I want to give you is an excuse to TLDR this post. So, I am quickly summarizing my adventures up until the present. The plan for the future is to make posts giving details to past events along with updating y’all on current happenings.
At twenty-four years of age, I have spent the last year and a half taking full advantage of the freedom bestowed upon me after finishing my eighteen year stint in the American education system.</description></item></channel></rss>